Yue KANG

Email:kangyue9323@gmail.com Address: NSW 2007

Experienced Full Stack Developer and web developer with a demonstrated history of working in the website development and content management systems. Skilled in frontend development and .Net Framework. Engineering background with a Master Degree in Software Engineering from Federation University Australia. Key deliverables include developing commercial websites in Html, CSS, JavaScript, React.Js. bootstrap, jQuery, Net Framework, C#, Sitecore and Optimizely

Key Skills Summary

Programming Languages: JavaScript/TypeScript, HTML5/CSS3, Python3, C#

Frameworks: .Net, React.js, Node.js, Vue.js

Libraries: BootStrap4/5, ¡Query, iTextSharp,TinyMCE5, Puppeteer

CMS: Sitecore, Optimizely(EpiServer), WordPress

Infrastructure: AWS Microservices, Azure DevOps, GitHub, GitLab, SQL Server

Design Platform: MS Visual Studio 2022/2019, VS code

API Architecture and tools: RESTful API, Postman

Language: Chinese(Native), English(Business)

Education

Master of Technology, major in Software Engineering

Federation University Australia

Achievements – GDP 6.188/7

Master of Arts

The Chinese University of Hong Kong

Bachelor of Philosophy

Tongji University

Employment History

Front-end Developer Oct.2023- Now

Project - Optimizely CMS Uplift - Frontend

- Collaborating with designers and product managers to understand the requirements of the user-stories
- Translating Figma designs into HTML/CSS/JS code in Vue.js framework
- Collaborating with back-end developers to integrate the frontend with backend, Actively participated in development activities, sprint planning and solution meetings.
- Tech Stacks: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Vue.js, Node.js, Tailwind, Liquid

Junior Full Stack Developer

Apr.2021-Sept.2023

Project – Optimizely CMS Migration

- Delivering the new website and working on CMS migration from Sitecore to Optimizely.
- Setup, integrated and developed TimyMCE as main rich text editor, and created free-text components.
- Troubleshoot and debug both in frontend and backend
- Tech Stacks: HTML, CSS, Node.js, .Net framework, Azure, AWS, Optimizely(Episerver), C#, JavaScript/TypeScript,

Yue KANG 1

Project – Sitecore BAU

- Maintained, developed and designed the new UI for construction tracker for all communities on a two-week basis, with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and React.js.
- Building and Maintaining the website. Key deliverables include creating custom form components such as image tiles, feature statement block and news tiles.
- Other deliverables include badge and ribbon redesign, cache refactoring, templates design, maintain CICD pipeline and writing scripts to identify and fix issues in integration services.
- Developed AWS Canary automatic testing scripts to verify regression tests by using puppeteer API.
- Tech stacks: JavaScript, CSS, HTML, C#, Node.js, .Net framework, Azure, AWS, Sitecore

Project – Sitecore Brand Refresh

- Scaled the website with company's brand uplift Strategy. Key deliverables including developing components such as headers, navigation bar, feature statement, Static HTML file and product brochure.
- Collaboration with UI designers, content editors, and testers to improve the customer experience and proactively review and action on risk consideration
- Maintained and developed components for an internal offer system in React framework
- Tech Stacks: JavaScript, HTML, CSS Node.js, .Net framework, Azure, AWS, Sitecore, C#,

IT Support Oct.2020-Apr.2021

- Produced content for e-commerce
- Collected and updated data in company's internal system
- Troubleshoot technical and content problems and provided solutions via phone, email and wechat
- Providing diary management support for general manager in fast-paced professional environment
- Assisting with presentations and client marketing strategies.

Software Engineer July.2020-Sept.2020

- Worked as a software engineer as the requirement from PE professional year.
- Developed Restful API and front-end for MT4 Manager API, with C#, Vue.js and Antdv
- Obtained keys from Redis and built an automatic html email sending structure with python
- Responsible for version control with Git and Bitbucket

IT Product Manager Intern

Mar.2020-June.2020

- Worked as a full time intern in Netroworx for project managements.
- Performed localization of 6 languages with Google Translation on the client's request
- Updated and maintained application's technical documentation with Jira
- Quality Assurance for Sologic an IOS application within established practices to ensure programs perform properly

Feel free to contact kangyue9323@gmail.com for more details! Welcome ~~~

Yue KANG 2